Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 10: Boxes 572-635
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 10: Boxes 572-635
- Western New York Federation of Labor, Publication (Box 635, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Western New York Federation of Labor News, 1971; Publication (Box 635, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.20:no.7 (1971:Oct.)
- HERE (Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union). Dining Room Employees Union, Local 1, Publication (Box 635, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Dining Room Employee, 1971; Publication (Box 635, Folder 14)
    Author: HERE (Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union). Dining Room Employees Union, Local 1
    Notes: v.19:no.8 (1971:Sep.)
  - Item 2: Dining Room Employee, 1971; Publication (Box 635, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.19:no.9 (1971:Oct.)
- Toy and Novelty Workers of America, Publication (Box 635, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Local 223 News, 1971; Publication (Box 635, Folder 15)
    Author: Toy and Novelty Workers of America
    Notes: v.8:no.3 (1971:Oct./Nov.)
- AFTRA (American Federation of Television and Radio Artists), Publication (Box 635, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Stand By!, 1971; Publication (Box 635, Folder 16)
    Notes: v.4:no.5 (1971:Sep./Oct.)
  - Item 2: Stand By!, 1971; Publication (Box 635, Folder 16)
    Notes: v.4:no.6 (1971:Nov./Dec.)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 635, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: By-laws of Local 837, 1972; Publication (Box 635, Folder 17)
    Author: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America. Industrial Workers Union, Local 837
  - Item 2: Summary Plan Description and Plan Booklet, 1977; Publication (Box 635, Folder 17)
    Author: United Paperworkers International Union. Paper Converters Local 286
    Notes: Booklet no.8
  - Item 3: Constitution, 1966; Publication (Box 635, Folder 17)
    Author: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America
  - Item 4: Employment Arbitration Plain and Fancy, 1979; Publication (Box 635, Folder 17)
    Author: AAA (American Arbitration Association)
  - Item 5: Constitution - 1978, Publication (Box 635, Folder 17)
    Author: Pennsylvania AFL- CIO
  - Item 6: By-laws of Local 732, Publication (Box 635, Folder 17)
    Author: International Brotherhood of Teamsters. Airline and Aerospace Employees Local Union no.732
  - Item 7: Federal motor carrier safety regulations, 1980; Publication (Box 635, Folder 17)
    Author: U.S. Department of Transportation. Federal Highway Administration
    Notes: Parts no. 390-397
  - Item 8: Retail Clerks, Eastern States, Health and Welfare Fund, Publication (Box 635, Folder 17)
    Author: Retail Clerks International Association
  - Item 9: Retail Clerks, Eastern States, Health and Welfare Fund: Benefit Booklet and Summary Plan Description, Publication (Box 635, Folder 17)
  - Item 10: Health and Welfare Benefit book: Summary Plan Description, 1985; Publication (Box 635, Folder 17)
  - Item 11: Health and Welfare Benefit book: Summary Plan Description, 1985; Publication (Box 635, Folder 17)
  - Item 12: The Pension Plan - Paper Converters, Local 286, 1976; Publication (Box 635, Folder 17)
  - Item 13: Teamsters Pension Plan of Philadelphia and Vicinity, 1986; Publication (Box 635, Folder 17)
  - Item 14: Teamsters Pension Plan of Philadelphia and Vicinity: Summary Plan Description. Your Pension benefits, 1980; Publication (Box 635, Folder 17)